{
    "subject": "resource/Longobardia",
    "predicate": "ontology/capital",
    "object": "resource/Bari",
    "human_readable": "The capital of Longobardia is Bari.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9308139681816101,
            "question": "Does Longobardia have a capital?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9253869652748108,
            "question": "What is the capital of Longobardia?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.726799726486206,
            "question": "Is Bari a capital city?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6531542539596558,
            "question": "Which region has Bari as its capital city?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.453482061624527,
            "question": "Where is Bari located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.43739622831344604,
            "question": "Can you name any other cities in Longobardia?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.34766727685928345,
            "question": "What is the history of Bari?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.25052356719970703,
            "question": "What is the population of Bari?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2338152378797531,
            "question": "What is the name of the region that Bari governs?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.16664639115333557,
            "question": "What are some important landmarks or attractions in Bari?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The capital of Longobardia is Bari.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8773_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of the region that Bari governs?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8773_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the population of Bari?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8773_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the history of Bari?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8773_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8773_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8773_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8773_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8773_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8773_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8773_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8773_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8773_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8773_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8773_72.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here is the response:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n\nExplanation: According to the provided context information, Bari was indeed a significant city and even the capital of various entities (e.g., Apulia region, Catapanate of Italy), but there is no direct mention that it was specifically the capital of Longobardia."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: According to the provided documents, Bari was indeed an important city with historical significance as part of the Catepanate of Italy and it does have a Romanesque architecture such as the Basilica of San Nicola. However, there is no information supporting that Bari served as the capital of Longobardia. The context mainly discusses Bari's role during the Norman conquest and its current status in Apulia, Southern Italy."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 0,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Most Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}